<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
    <name>EBSG - Anomaly Genes</name>
    <author>alite</author>
    <packageId>EBSG.Anomaly</packageId>
    <supportedVersions>
        <li>1.5</li>
    </supportedVersions>
    
    <modDependencies>
        <li>
            <packageId>ludeon.rimworld.biotech</packageId>
            <displayName>Biotech</displayName>
        </li>
        <li>
            <packageId>ludeon.rimworld.anomaly</packageId>
            <displayName>Anomaly</displayName>
        </li>
    </modDependencies>

    <loadAfter>
        <li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Royalty</li>
        <li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Ideology</li>
        <li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Biotech</li>
        <li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Anomaly</li>
        <li>EBSG.Framework</li>
    </loadAfter>

    <description>
Expanded Biotech Style Genes(EBSG) is the step beyond [url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2985153870]More Biotech Style Genes[/url]. Where that series sought to expand ranges that already exist, this series seeks to add ranges that should exist. You get gene ranges that alter sleep fall rate, but why not a range for changing the rate it recovers? If you can have fire resistance genes, why not have genes to resist other types of damage like frostbite and acid?

This mod adds some basic Anomaly based genes to the game for players to pick from. 8 of them alter how quickly and efficiently the pawn can study anomalies, 9 of them impact how quickly the carrier can suppress anomalies, and two of them add a special hediff from the DLC (inhumanized and void born). The Void Born gene requires archites be visible, is placed next to the inhumanized gene, and will be available even if you do not have [url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=3039936922]Expanded Archite Genes[/url].

IMPORTANT NOTE: Both Inhumanized and Void Born require the [url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=3112549163]EBSG Framework[/url]. This mod will still work without the framework, you just won't have those two genes available. If you do have the framework and can't find the genes, make sure you have ignore restrictions active, and are looking in the EBSG - Anomaly section.

Why did I pick these names for the genes? Honestly, because I didn't really have any other ideas. The idea department had mostly burnt down before I started trying to figure out stuff for this one.

Included in [url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=3020821838]Expanded Biotech Style Genes - All in One[/url].

[url=https://discord.gg/fYP8qkcNDh]Discord link[/url] for those who want an easier way to ask questions, make requests, or just chat. I'll also be posting new releases there.

[url=https://steamcommunity.com/id/alite/myworkshopfiles/?appid=294100]Easy link to all of my Rimworld mods[/url]

[url=https://github.com/KonradHeinser/][img]https://i.imgur.com/kTkpTOE.png[/img][/url]
[url=https://ko-fi.com/alite56114][img]https://i.imgur.com/Utx6OIH.png[/img][/url]
  </description>
</ModMetaData>

<!--Original textures for gene icons are available on https://game-icons.net-->
